https://www.schramminc.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Schramm Inc’s policy to
respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.schramminc.com, and other sites we own and operate.
1. Information we collect
Log data
When you visit our website, our servers may automatically log the
standard data provided by your web browser. It may include your
computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and
version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time
spent on each page, and other details.
Device data
We may also collect data about the device you’re using to access our
website. This data may include the device type, operating system, unique
device identifiers, device settings, and geo-location data. What we
collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and
software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer
or software provider to learn what information they make available to
us.
Personal information
We may ask for personal information, such as your:
NameEmailSocial media profilesDate of birthPhone/mobile numberHome/Mailing addressWork addressWebsite addressPayment information
2. Legal bases for processing
We will process your personal information lawfully, fairly and in a
transparent manner. We collect and process information about you only
where we have legal bases for doing so.
These legal bases depend on the services you use and how you use them, meaning we collect and use your information only where:
it’s necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a
party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a
contract (for example, when we provide a service you request from us);it satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your
data protection interests), such as for research and development, to
market and promote our services, and to protect our legal rights and
interests;you give us consent to do so for a specific purpose (for example, you might consent to us sending you our newsletter); orwe need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.
Where you consent to our use of information about you for a specific
purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time (but this
will not affect any processing that has already taken place).
We don’t keep personal information for longer than is necessary.
While we retain this information, we will protect it within commercially
acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised
access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we advise
that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure and
cannot guarantee absolute data security. If necessary, we may retain
your personal information for our compliance with a legal obligation or
in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of
another natural person.
3. Collection and use of information
We may collect, hold, use and disclose information for the following
purposes and personal information will not be further processed in a
manner that is incompatible with these purposes:
to process any transactional or ongoing payments;to deliver products and/or services to you;to enable you to access and use our website, associated applications and associated social media platforms;to contact and communicate with you;for internal record keeping and administrative purposes;for analytics, market research and business development, including
to operate and improve our website, associated applications and
associated social media platforms;for advertising and marketing, including to send you promotional
information about our products and services and information about third
parties that we consider may be of interest to you; andto comply with our legal obligations and resolve any disputes that we may have.
4. Disclosure of personal information to third parties
We may disclose personal information to:
third party service providers for the purpose of enabling them to
provide their services, including (without limitation) IT service
providers, data storage, hosting and server providers, ad networks,
analytics, error loggers, debt collectors, maintenance or
problem-solving providers, marketing or advertising providers,
professional advisors and payment systems operators;our employees, contractors and/or related entities;sponsors or promoters of any competition we run;credit reporting agencies, courts, tribunals and regulatory
authorities, in the event you fail to pay for goods or services we have
provided to you;third parties, including agents or sub-contractors, who assist us in
providing information, products, services or direct marketing to you;
andthird parties to collect and process data.
5. International transfers of personal information
The personal information we collect is stored and processed in
Canada, or where we or our partners, affiliates and third-party
providers maintain facilities. By providing us with your personal
information, you consent to the disclosure to these overseas third
parties.
We will ensure that any transfer of personal information from
countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to countries outside the
EEA will be protected by appropriate safeguards, for example by using
standard data protection clauses approved by the European Commission, or
the use of binding corporate rules or other legally accepted means.
Where we transfer personal information from a non-EEA country to
another country, you acknowledge that third parties in other
jurisdictions may not be subject to similar data protection laws to the
ones in our jurisdiction. There are risks if any such third party
engages in any act or practice that would contravene the data privacy
laws in our jurisdiction and this might mean that you will not be able
to seek redress under our jurisdiction’s privacy laws.
6. Your rights and controlling your personal information
Choice and consent: By providing personal
information to us, you consent to us collecting, holding, using and
disclosing your personal information in accordance with this privacy
policy. If you are under 16 years of age, you must have, and warrant to
the extent permitted by law to us, that you have your parent or legal
guardian’s permission to access and use the website and they (your
parents or guardian) have consented to you providing us with your
personal information. You do not have to provide personal information to
us, however, if you do not, it may affect your use of this website or
the products and/or services offered on or through it.
Information from third parties: If we receive
personal information about you from a third party, we will protect it as
set out in this privacy policy. If you are a third party providing
personal information about somebody else, you represent and warrant that
you have such person’s consent to provide the personal information to
us.
Restrict: You may choose to restrict the collection
or use of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to us
using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may
change your mind at any time by contacting us using the details below.
If you ask us to restrict or limit how we process your personal
information, we will let you know how the restriction affects your use
of our website or products and services.
Access and data portability: You may request details
of the personal information that we hold about you. You may request a
copy of the personal information we hold about you. Where possible, we
will provide this information in CSV format or other easily readable
machine format. You may request that we erase the personal information
we hold about you at any time. You may also request that we transfer
this personal information to another third party.
Correction: If you believe that any information we
hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or
misleading, please contact us using the details below. We will take
reasonable steps to correct any information found to be inaccurate,
incomplete, misleading or out of date.
Notification of data breaches: We will comply laws applicable to us in respect of any data breach.
Complaints: If you believe that we have breached a
relevant data protection law and wish to make a complaint, please
contact us using the details below and provide us with full details of
the alleged breach. We will promptly investigate your complaint and
respond to you, in writing, setting out the outcome of our investigation
and the steps we will take to deal with your complaint. You also have
the right to contact a regulatory body or data protection authority in
relation to your complaint.
Unsubscribe: To unsubscribe from our e-mail database
or opt-out of communications (including marketing communications),
please contact us using the details below or opt-out using the opt-out
facilities provided in the communication.
7. Cookies
We use “cookies” to collect information about you and your activity
across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website
stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit, so we can
understand how you use our site. This helps us serve you content based
on preferences you have specified. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for
more information.
8. Business transfers
If we or our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go
out of business or enter bankruptcy, we would include data among the
assets transferred to any parties who acquire us. You acknowledge that
such transfers may occur, and that any parties who acquire us may
continue to use your personal information according to this policy.
9. Limits of our policy
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us.
Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of
those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their
respective privacy practices.
10. Changes to this policy
At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect
current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let users
know about changes via our website. Your continued use of this site
after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our
practices around privacy and personal information.
If we make a significant change to this privacy policy, for example
changing a lawful basis on which we process your personal information,
we will ask you to re-consent to the amended privacy policy.
This policy is effective as of 1 January 2020.
